Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records
1872-2016
RU 507
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
64.17
(86 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, scrapbooks, ledgers, financial records, press releases, and annual reports documenting athletics at Yale. Topics include varsity and intramural sports, physical education, the Payne Whitney Gymnasium, fundraising for facilities, anthropomorphic measurements of students, and the effects of World War I on Yale athletics. The records of Robert N. Corwin as chairmain of the board of control of the Yale University Athletic Association and Delaney Kiphuth as director are also included.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics, Physical Education, and Recreation
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-A (YRG 38-A), Records documenting administration of Yale athletic and physical education programs.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Existence and Location of Copies
Scrapbooks are available on microfilm from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, at cost. Order no. HM194. 1985. 1556 frames on 2 reels, 35mm.
Biographical / Historical
The Yale Athletic Association (later known as the Yale University Athletic Association) had its first meeting in 1872. It became the Yale University Department of Athletics, Physical Education, and Recreation circa 1966.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, scrapbooks, ledgers, financial records, press releases, and annual reports documenting athletics at Yale. Topics include varsity and intramural sports, physical education, the Payne Whitney Gymnasium, fundraising for facilities, anthropomorphic measurements of students, and the effects of World War I on Yale athletics. The records of Robert N. Corwin as chairmain of the board of control of the Yale University Athletic Association and Delaney Kiphuth as director are also included.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Athletics; College sports -- Management; College sports; Fund raising; Intramural sports; Physical education and training; Universities and colleges -- Departments; Scrapbooks; Corwin, Robert Nelson, 1864-1944; Kiphuth, Delaney; Yale University Athletic Association; Yale University -- History -- 20th Century; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics, Physical Education, and Recreation
- Records, 1872-1941; Accession 19ND-A-367
  - Committees
    - Athletic Grounds, Committee on, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Inquiry on Athletics, Committee on, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda
    - 1913 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1914 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1915 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1916 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1924 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sports Correspondence and Data
    - Baseball, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
    - Basketball, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Boxing, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Crew (Box 2)
      - Photograph of boat house built in 1860, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Statistics, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Regatta correspondence, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Derby Day, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Regatta, Long Beach, California, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Yale-Harvard boat race, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Fencing, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Football (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - President's book: Football Association, 1872-1884 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Harvard, 1888-1891 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Stagg, Alonzo A., 1889 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Telegram from Princeton re: Bruce Caldwell, 1927 November (Box 3, Folder 24A)
      - Cummock, A. J., 1889-1891 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Chronology, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Press ticket requests, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
      - Press ticket requests, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 29-32)
      - Press ticket requests, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 33-34)
      - Freshman statistics, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - 1933-1934 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - 1935 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - 1936 (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
      - 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Golf, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Hockey, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Lacrosse, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Polo (Box 6)
      - Indoor, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - Outdoor, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - Water, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Rugby, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Schedules: miscellaneous sports, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Soccer: Yale-Penn game, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Squash, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Swimming, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Tennis, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Track and Cross Country
      - Interscholastic records, 1914-1934 (Box 6, Folder 53)
        - 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 54)
        - 1931-1934 (Box 6, Folder 55)
        - 1933 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Wrestling, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Memorabilia (Box 6)
      - Printing block with football play on it, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Financial records
    - Chart of expenses, 1894-1905 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Committee of 21: Construction of Yale Bowl
      - Executive Committee minutes, 1911-1917 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Correspondence, memoranda, 1912-1915 (Box 8, Folder 61-64)
      - Athletic Association - Sperry Engineering Co. Contract 374 (Yale Bowl), 1920-1921 (Box 9, Folder 65-69)
        - 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 70)
        - 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 71)
        - 1935-1937 (Box 10, Folder 72)
        - Miscellaneous, 1915-1936, undated (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Ledgers
      - Receipts: major and minor sports, 1931-1936 (Box 11)
      - Receipts: gate guaranty, rentals, Tennis and property, programs, Team Trips, Telephone and Telegrams, Equipment and supplies, 1936-1940 (Box 12)
      - Disbursements: major and minor sports, 1935 (Box 13)
      - Disbursements: A.A.A., property accounts, golf course and maintenance, Ray Thompkins grill, coaches' salaries and expenses, health team equipment, team trips, buses, visiting team expenses, officials, league dues, entry fees, awards and banquets, office expenses, printing and advertising, intramural athletics, sundry accounts, 1935-1939 (Box 14)
      - Disbursements: same as above, 1939-1941 (Box 15)
      - Cash sheets: gate and guaranty, rentals, tennis and property, programs, team trips, telephone and telegrams, equipment and supplies, 1940-1941 (Box 16)
- Annual reports, 1948-1982; Accession 19ND-A-368
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2017
  Scope and Contents
  Includes annual reports of the Athletic Association, Intercollegiate Athletics, and Payne Whitney Gymnasium.
  - Annual reports
    - 1948-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1-12)
    - 1962-1972 (Box 2, Folder 13-22)
    - 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 23-27)
    - 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 28-34)
- Administrative Manual, 1929-1933; Accession 19ND-A-505
  The materials are open for research.
  Contains information about tickets, facility arrangement, security, etc.
  - Administrative Manual, 1929-1933 (Box 1)
- Records of Robert N. Corwin as chariman, 1912-1919; Accession 1960-A-005
  - Correspondence
    - Adee, George T, 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Allen, Frederic W, 1914-1915 April (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Allen, Frederic W., 1915 May-November (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Allen, Frederic W., 1916 February-June (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Allen, Frederic W., 1916 July-December (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Allen, Frederic W., 1917 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Allen, Frederic W., 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Anderson, William G., 1915-1919 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Atwood, Thomas C., 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - A, 1915-1919 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bakewell, Charles M., 1915 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Briggs, LeBaron R., 1915-1916 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Briggs, LeBaron R., 1917 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Briggs, LeBaron, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - B, 1915-1916 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - B, 1917-1920 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Camp, Walter, 1915-1918 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Carter, Walter F., 1916-1919 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Case, George B., 1915-1916 July (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Case, George B., 1916 September-1919 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Cuyler, Thomas DeWitt, 1915-1919 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - C, 1913-1919 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Danford, Robert M., 1917 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Day, George Parmly, 1915-1916 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Day, George Parmly, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - D, 1915-1919 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - E, 1915-1919 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Fisher, Samuel, 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - F, 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Griggs, Robert Wadsworth, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - G, 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Hadley, Arthur T., 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Hartwell, John A., 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Harvard Athletic Association, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Hobson, Henry W., 1915-1918 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Hyatt, Alton Rufus, 1915-1918 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - H, 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - I, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Johnson, Frederic B., 1916-1919 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Jones, Frederick S., 1914-1918 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - J, 1914-1918 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Kirby, Gustavus S., 1916-1919 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - K, 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - L, 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - McClenahan, Howard, 1915-1917 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - McClenahan, Howard, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - McCormick, Vance C., 1915-1918 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Mc, 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Mason, George G., 1915-1917 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Meigs, Dwight R., 1916-1917 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Moore, Fred W., 1915-1917 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Morgan, Ralph, 1915-1919 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - M, 1915-1920 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Nicholson, Frederick W., 1914-1920 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - N, 1915-1918 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Oviatt, Edwin, 1915-1919 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - O, 1915-1919 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - P, 1915-1920 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Queal, William, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - R, 1915-1919 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Sharpe, Albert R., 1919 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Stackpole, Edward J., Jr., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1915-1919 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Sweeney, Michael R., 1916-1917 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - S, 1915-1919 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Thompson, Everard, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Thorne, S. Brinckerhoff, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Tracy, John C., 1916-1917 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - T, 1915-1918 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - U-V, 1917-1919 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Winters, Edward J., 1916-1917 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - W, 1915-1919 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - X-Y-Z, 1918-1919 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Subject Files
    - Adee Memorial Boat Rouse, 1917-1919 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Athletic activity during World War I, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Athletic club house, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Athletic survey from the University of Washington, 1916 October 25 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Baseball, 1915-1919 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Baseball cage, 1916-1918 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Baseball "coach on the bench" issue, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Basketball, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Board of Control of the Yale University Athletic Association, 1915-1920 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Board of Control, executive committee: minutes of meetings, 1916-1917 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Bowling, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Cancellation of athletic schedules during World War I, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Crew, 1915-1919 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Eligibility rules for athletics, 1915-1919 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Eligibility for athletics: exceptions to military rule, 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Eligibility for athletics: special cases, 1915-1918 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Eligibility for athletics: Harry LeGore et al. case, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Eligibility for athletics: Harry LeGore et al. case, 1916 January (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Eligibility for athletics: Harry LeGore et al. case, 1916 February-July (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Eligibility for Athletics: Harvard - Yale - Princeton agreement, 1915-1916 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Eligibility for athletics: Thomas Enwright case, 1915-1917 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Fencing, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Football: coaches, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Football: coaches, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Football: reorganization, 1912-1917, undated (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Football: scheduling, 1915-1919 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Football: search for a head coach, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Football: squad list and itinerary, 1917, undated (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Football: two reprints, undated (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Freshmen athletics, 1915-1916, undated (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Golf, 1915; 1918 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Gymnastic team, 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Hockey, 1915-1919, undated (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Lacrosse, 1915-1918 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Major sports: schedules and committee members, 1917-1919 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Maltby Ave. closing, 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Managers: rules for election, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Medical examination of athletics, 1915-1916; 1919 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Minor Sports Association, 1915-1919 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Soccer, 1915-1919 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Speeches and other writings by Robert Corwin, undated (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Swimming, 1916-1919 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Team captains and managers; team statistics; design of varsity letter uniforms, 1917-1918, undated (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Tennis, 1916-1919 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Ticket office, 1915-1920 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Track, 1916-1920 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Track: Yale-Harvard dual cup, 1916-1917 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Training tables comittee, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Undergraduate comittee of the Yale University Athletic Association, 1917-1919 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - University Board of Health, 1916-1919 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - Wrestling, 1916-1918 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Yale athletic fields: listing of land which could be used by Agricultural Service, 1917 May (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Yale Committee of 21 (for the development of athletic facilities at Yale), 1915-1918 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - Yale Corporation Prudential Committee decisions concerning athletics, 1915-1919 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Yale Daily News: correspondence and news releases, 1915-1919 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - Yale lettermen in military Service, 1917-1918 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Yale University Athletic Association: annual reports and balance sheets, 1915-1918 (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - Yale University Athletic Association: early drafts of Constitution and articles of incorporation, 1961, undated (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Yale University Athletic Association: financial statements, related correspondence, 1911-1918 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Yale University Athletic Association: minutes of meetings, 1913-1917, undated (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Yale University Athletic Association: reorganization, 1911; 1916 (Box 10, Folder 134)
- Records of student measurements, including anthropometric and fitness, 1883-1950; Accession 2005-A-054 (Box 1–9)
  No inventory available.
- Administrative records, including cashbooks & receipts, circa 1879-1978; Accession 2005-A-055
  - Correspondence - Basketball, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cashbook, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cashbook, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Hints to Managers" wrestling, circa1895 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Hints to Managers" boxing, circa 1920 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Receipt book, 1879-1884 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Athletic Dept. policies and concepts, 1954-1987; Accession 2006-A-003
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  1 bound volume.
  - Policies and concepts, 1954-1987 (Box 1)
- Sports Information Office press releases, 1948-1992; Accession 2006-A-005
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Press releases
    - 1948-1949 (Box 8)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 1)
    - 1957-1966 (Box 2)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 3)
    - 1974-1978 (Box 6)
    - 1979 (Box 7)
    - 1980-1984 (Box 4)
    - 1984-1984 (Box 5)
    - 1988-1992 (Box 8)
- Records of intercollegiate athletics, 1942-1974; Accession 2006-A-027
  Arranged by sport.
  - Baseball
    - Attendance, 1942-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1-11)
    - Freshman Intramural Athletics
      - Attendance, 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12-16)
      - General, 1947-1951 (Box 1, Folder 17-21)
      - Reports, 1948-1952 (Box 1, Folder 22-24)
    - General, 1942-1950 (Box 1, Folder 25-34)
    - Reports, 1944, 1948, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 35-37)
  - Basketball
    - Attendance, 1942-1950 (Box 1, Folder 38-44)
    - Freshman Intramural
      - Attendance, 1946-1952 (Box 1, Folder 45-50)
      - General, 1946-1952 (Box 1, Folder 51-56)
      - High scorers, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 57-58)
      - Reports, 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 59-67)
    - General, 1942-1950 (Box 1, Folder 68-74)
    - Graduate schools league, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - High scorers, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 76-77)
    - Reports, 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 78-81)
    - Second team games, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Boxing
    - Attendance, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Freshman Intramurals
      - Attendance, 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 84-88)
      - General, 1946-1951 (Box 1, Folder 89-93)
      - Reports, 1946-1952 (Box 1, Folder 94-99)
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Crew
    - Attendance, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Football
    - Attendance, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Freshman Intramurals
      - Attendance, 1946-1950 (Box 1, Folder 106-109)
      - General, 1946-1950 (Box 1, Folder 110-113)
      - Reports, 1946-1950 (Box 1, Folder 114-117)
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Golf
    - Attendance, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Freshman Intramurals
      - Attendance, 1947-1951 (Box 1, Folder 121-125)
      - General, 1947-1951 (Box 1, Folder 126-130)
      - Reports, 1947-1951 (Box 1, Folder 131-135)
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 136)
    - Paul Haviland Memorial Golf Tournament, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 137)
    - Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Handball
    - Attendance, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 139)
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 140)
    - Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Hockey
    - Attendance, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Freshman Intramurals
      - Attendance, 1946-1952 (Box 2, Folder 143-148)
      - General, 1946-1952 (Box 2, Folder 149-154)
      - Reports, 1946-1952 (Box 2, Folder 155-160)
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Lacrosse
    - Attendance, 1943-1946 (Box 2, Folder 163-168)
    - Equipment inventory, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - General, 1942-1946 (Box 2, Folder 170-177)
  - Reports, 1943-1946 (Box 2, Folder 178-184)
    - Stationery, Circa 1950 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - Polo, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - Soccer
    - Attendance, 1942-1950 (Box 2, Folder 187-199)
    - General, 1942-1950 (Box 2, Folder 200-212)
    - Reports, 1942-1950 (Box 2, Folder 213-225)
  - Softball
    - Attendance, 1942-1950 (Box 2, Folder 226-234)
    - Freshman Intramurals
      - Attendance, 1947-1952 (Box 2, Folder 235-240)
      - General, 1947-1951 (Box 2, Folder 241-245)
      - Reports, 1947-1952 (Box 2, Folder 246-250)
    - General, 1942-1950 (Box 2, Folder 251-260)
    - Reports, 1944, 1948-1950 (Box 2, Folder 261-263)
  - Squash
    - Attendance, 1942-1950 (Box 2, Folder 264-271)
    - Freshman Intramurals
      - Attendance, 1946-1952 (Box 2, Folder 272-277)
      - Racquets, 1946-1952 (Box 2, Folder 278-283)
      - Reports, 1946-1952 (Box 2, Folder 284-289)
    - General, 1942-1943, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 290-292)
    - Racquets, 1944-1950 (Box 2, Folder 293-297)
    - Reports, 1942-1945 (Box 2, Folder 298-301)
    - Reports, 1946-1950 (Box 3, Folder 302-305)
    - Tournaments, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 306)
    - Varsity, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 307-308)
  - Swimming
    - Attendance, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 309-315)
    - Freshman Intramurals
      - Attendance, 1949-1952 (Box 3, Folder 316-318)
      - General, 1949-1952 (Box 3, Folder 319-321)
      - Reports, 1949-1952 (Box 3, Folder 322-324)
      - Series I
        - Attendance, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 325-326)
        - General, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 327-329)
        - Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 330-332)
      - Series II
        - Attendance, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 333-334)
        - General, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 335-337)
        - Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 338-340)
    - General, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 341-349)
    - Reports, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 350-356)
    - Tournament, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 357-358)
  - Tennis
    - Attendance, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 359-369)
    - Freshman Intramurals
      - Attendance, 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 370-375)
      - General, 1947-1951 (Box 3, Folder 376-380)
      - Reports, 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 381-386)
    - General, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 387-398)
    - Reports, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 399-409)
    - Tournaments, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 410)
    - Varsity, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 411-413)
  - Touch football
    - Attendance, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 414-421)
    - Freshman Intramurals
      - Attendance, 1946-1952 (Box 3, Folder 422-427)
      - General, 1946-1952 (Box 3, Folder 428-433)
      - Reports, 1946-1952 (Box 4, Folder 434-439)
    - General, 1942-1950 (Box 4, Folder 440-447)
    - Records, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 448)
    - Reports, 1942-1950 (Box 4, Folder 449-455)
  - Track
    - Cross country race, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 456)
    - General, 1944-1946 (Box 4, Folder 457-460)
  - Wrestling
    - Attendance, 1944-1950 (Box 4, Folder 461-466)
    - Freshman intramurals
      - Attendance, 1947-1951 (Box 4, Folder 467-470)
      - General, 1946-1951 (Box 4, Folder 471-475)
      - Reports, 1946-1951 (Box 4, Folder 476-480)
    - General, 1942-1950 (Box 4, Folder 481-487)
    - Reports, 1942-1950 (Box 4, Folder 488-494)
  - General
    - All-around championship, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 495)
    - Alumni, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 496)
    - Articles, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 497)
    - Athletic secretaries, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 498)
    - Bills, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 499)
    - Bureau of Appointments, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 500)
    - Charms, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 501)
    - College directories, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 502)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, notes, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 503)
    - Correspondence with Harvard, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 504)
    - Eligibility rules, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 505)
    - Employees in Intramural Department, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 506)
    - Equipment, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 507)
    - Freshman Intramural
      - All Year Championship, 1948-1952 (Box 4, Folder 508-511)
      - Athletic secretaries, 1946-1952 (Box 4, Folder 512-516)
      - Bulletin board sheets, Circa 1950 (Box 4, Folder 517)
      - Charms, 1946-1951 (Box 4, Folder 518-522)
      - General, 1946-1952 (Box 4, Folder 523-528)
    - Freshman office, 1946-1952 (Box 4, Folder 529-534)
    - Freshman program, 1946-1952 (Box 4, Folder 535-540)
    - Freshman sports captains, 1946-1952 (Box 4, Folder 541-546)
    - General warning lists, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 547)
    - Graduate school athletics, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 548)
    - Gymnasium correspondence (Mr. Oscar Kiphuth), 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 549)
    - Harvard House athletics, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 550)